Guide to the Stanford Daily [microform] 7900
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
The Stanford Daily [microform]
1892-2009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
7900
127 microfilm reel(s)
Stamp description
Stanford University, Calif.
General Note
"An independent newspaper."
Stanford University; Stanford University
- Microfilm reels
  - Vol. 161A, Vol. 163, 1972 Jun - 1973 Jun (Box 1)
  - Vol. 163A, Vol 164, 1973 Jun - 1974 Feb (Box 1)
  - Vol. 165, 166, 1974 Feb - 1975 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 167, 168, 1975 Feb - 1976 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 169, 169A, 170, 1976 Feb - 1977 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 171, 1977 Jan - Jun (Box 1)
  - Vol. 180-181, 1981 Sep - 1982 Mar (Box 1)
  - Vol. 181, 181A, 182, 1982 Apr - 1983 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 183, 1983 Jan - Aug (Box 1)
  - Vol. 184, 1983 Sep - 1984 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 185, 1984 Jan 30 - Jun 6 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 185 A, 1984 Jun 26 - 1984 Aug 24 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 186, 1984 Sep 24 - 1985 Feb 1 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 187, 1985 Feb 4 - Jun 16 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 187A, 189A, 191A, 1985 Jun 25 - 1987 Aug 21 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 188, 1985 Sep 23 - 1986 Jan 24 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 189, 1986 Jan 27 - 1986 Jun 4 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 190, 1986 Sep 29 - 1987 Jan 30 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 191 (+ Commencement Issue), 1987 Feb 2 - Jun 3 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1987 Sep 23 - 1988 Jan 29 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1988 Feb 1 - Aug 19 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1988 Sep 21 - 1989 Jan 31 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1989 Jun 29 - Aug 24 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1989 Sep 21 - 1990 Feb 2 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1990 Jun 28 - Aug 23 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1990 Sep 20 - 1991 Feb 1 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1991 Feb 4 - Jun 16 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1991 Sep 19 - 1992 Jan 31 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1992 Feb 3 - Jun 14 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1992 Sep 24 - 1993 Jan 29 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1993 Feb 1 - Jun 11 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1993 Sep 23 - 1994 Jan 28 (Box 1)
  - Orig., 1994 Jun 23 - Aug 18 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 206, 1994 Sep 22 - 1995 Feb (Box 1)
  - Vol. 208, 1995 Sep 22 - 1996 Feb 2 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 207, 1995 Feb 6 - 1995 Jun 15 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 208A, 1995 Jun 29 - 1995 Aug 29 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 209, Vol. 210A, 1996 Feb - Aug (Box 1)
  - Vol. 214, 1998 Sep 18 - 1999 Jan 29 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 215, 1999 Feb - Jun (Box 1)
  - Vol. 218, 2000 Sep - Dec (Box 1)
  - Vol. 219, 2001 Jan - Jun (Box 1)
  - Vol. 220A - 220, 2001 Jul - Dec (Box 1)
  - Vol. 221, 2002 Feb - Jun 14 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 220, 2002 Jan - Feb (Box 1)
  - Vol. 222, 222A, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 223, 2003 Feb - Jun (Box 1)
  - Vol. 224, 2003- 2004 Jan 30 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 225, 226A, 2004 Feb - Sep (Box 1)
  - Vol. 226, 2004 Sep 22 - 2005 Jan 28 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 227, 228A, 2005 Jan 31 - Sep 1 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 228, 2005 Sep - 2006 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 229, 230A, 2006 Jan -2007 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 232, 2007 Sep - 2008 Jan (Box 1)
  - Vol. 231, 232A, 2007 Sep - Feb (Box 1)
  - Vol. 233, 2008 Feb - Jun (Box 1)
  - Vol. 234A, 2008 Jul - Aug 28 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 234, 2008 Sep 16- 2009 Jan 30 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 235, 2009 Feb - Jun 12 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 172, 173 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 173, 174, 175 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 175, Vol. 176 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 178, 179, 179A, 1891 Jan - Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 1, 2, 3, 4, 1892 Sep - 1894 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 17, 18, 19, 20, 1900 Sep - 1902 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 21 through Vol. 24, 1902 Sep - 1904 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 25 through Vol. 28, 1904 Aug - 1906 Apr (Box 2)
  - Vol. 29 through 32, 1906 Aug - 1908 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 33 through 36, 1908 Sep - 1910 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 37 through 40, 1910 Aug - 1912 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 41 through 44, 1912 Aug - 1914 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 45 through Vol. 48, 1914 Sep - 1916 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 49 through Vol. 53, 1916 Aug - 1918 Jun (Box 2)
  - Vol. 54 through Vol. 57, 1918 Sep - 1920 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 54 through V. 57, 1918 Sep - 1920 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 58 through Vol. 60, 1920 Oct - 1922 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 61 through Vol. 63, 1922 Feb - 1923 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 64 through Vol. 66, 1923 Oct - 1925 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 67 through 69, 1925 Feb - 1926 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 70 through Vol. 72, 1926 Sep - 1928 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 73, 73A through 75, 1928 Feb - 1929 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 76 - 78, 1929 Oct - 1931 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 79, 79A through 81, 81A, 1931 Feb - 1932 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 82, 83, 1932 Oct - 1933 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 84 thru 86, 1933 Oct - 1935 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 87, 87A, 88, 1935 Feb - 1936 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 89, 90, 1936 Feb - 1937 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 91, 91A, 92, 1937 Feb - 1938 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 93, 93A, 94, 1938 Jan - 1939 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 95, 95A, 96, 1939 Feb - 1940 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 97, 97A, 98, 1940 Aug - 1941 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 99, 99A, 100, 1941 Feb - 1942 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 101 through 103, 1942 Feb - 1943 Jun (Box 2)
  - Vol. 104 through 106, 1943 Jun - 1944 Dec (Box 2)
  - Vol. 107, 107A, through 109, 110, 1945 Jan - 1946 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 110X, 111, 111A, 1946 Sep - 1947 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 112, 113, 1947 Sep - 1948 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 114, 115, 115A, 1948 Sep - 1949 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 116, 117, 177A, 1949 Sep - 1950 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 118 through 120, 1950 Sep - 1952 Feb (Box 2)
  - Vol. 121, 121A, 122, 1952 Feb - 1953 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 123, 123A through 125, 125A, 1953 Feb - 1954 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 126, 127, 128, 1954 Sep - 1956 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 129, 130, 131, 1956 Jan - 1957 Jul (Box 2)
  - Vol. 132, 133, 134, 1957 Sep - 1959 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 135, 136, 137, 1959 Feb - 1960 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol. 144, 146, 1963 Sep - 1965 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 147, 149, 1965 Feb - 1966 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vol. 150, 151A, 1966 Sep - 1968 Jan (Box 2)
  - V. 152, 153, 1967 Sep - 1968 Aug (Box 2)
  - V. 3 Stanford Daily Magazine, Vol. 155A, 1968 Feb - 1969 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol 156, 157, 1969 Sep - 1970 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 158, 159A, 1970 Sep - 1971 Aug (Box 2)
  - Vol 160, 161, 1971 Sep - 1972 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 171a, 177, 178, 1977 Jun - 1980 Nov (Box 2)
  - Vol. 5, 6, 7, 8, 1984 Sep - 1986 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 9, 10, 11, 12, 1986 Sep - 1989 May (Box 2)
  - Vol. 13, 14, 15, 16, 1989 Sep - 1900 May (Box 2)
  - Master, 1996 Sep 20 - Dec 4 (Box 2)
  - Master, 1997 Apr 1 - Aug 21 (Box 2)
  - Master, 1997 Jan 6 - Mar 31 (Box 2)
  - Master, 1997 Sep 19 - Dec 3 (Box 2)
  - Master, 1998 Apr 1 - Aug 20 (Box 2)
  - Master, 1998 Jan 5 - Mar 31 (Box 2)
  - Vol. 216, 1999 Sep 17 - 2000 Jan 31 (Box 2)
  - Vol. 217, 217A, 2000 Jul - Aug (Box 2)
  - unlabeled (Box 2)